<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Products on Max PVC</title><link>https://kumar-muthu.github.io/max-pvc/products/</link><description>Recent content in Products on Max PVC</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 21:45:33 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kumar-muthu.github.io/max-pvc/products/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EVA/PEVA Heat seal and Stitching bags</title><link>https://kumar-muthu.github.io/max-pvc/products/product-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 21:45:33 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://kumar-muthu.github.io/max-pvc/products/product-4/</guid><description>EVA or PEVA heat sealing and stitching can be done for two piece bags and pouches, it can be added up with pockets for insert cards, single or multi color printing, red sealking, white sealking, snap buttons, hangers, D handles, metal rings, velcro, recylce logos and even more as per the requirement. Below are some of our previous samples. We can customize as per the requirements.</description></item><item><title>Hangers</title><link>https://kumar-muthu.github.io/max-pvc/products/product-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 21:45:33 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://kumar-muthu.github.io/max-pvc/products/product-5/</guid><description>We provide a wide variety of hangers and Jhooks in different shapes, colors and sizes. Below are some of the hangers we deal with on daily basis</description></item><item><title>PVC Heat Seal bags and pouches</title><link>https://kumar-muthu.github.io/max-pvc/products/product-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 21:45:33 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://kumar-muthu.github.io/max-pvc/products/product-1/</guid><description>PVC heat sealing can be done for two piece bags and pouches, it can be added up with pockets for insert cards, single or multi color printing, red sealking, white sealking, plastic snap buttons, metal buttons, hangers, D handles, Zip lock, pressure locks, metal rings, velcro, recylce logos and even more as per the requirement. Below are some of our previous samples. We also own certification for Prof-65 quality PVC material.</description></item><item><title>PVC Zipper bags and pouches</title><link>https://kumar-muthu.github.io/max-pvc/products/product-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 21:45:33 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://kumar-muthu.github.io/max-pvc/products/product-2/</guid><description>PVC stitching can be done for two piece bags and pouches, it can be added up with pockets for insert cards, single or multi color printing, plastic snap buttons, metal buttons, hangers, D handles, Zip lock, metal rings, recylce logos and even more as per the requirement. Below are some of our previous samples. We also own certification for Prof-65 quality PVC material. We can customize as per the requirements.</description></item><item><title>Rigit Tops, Boxes and Sheets</title><link>https://kumar-muthu.github.io/max-pvc/products/product-6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 21:45:33 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://kumar-muthu.github.io/max-pvc/products/product-6/</guid><description>Rigid Tops, Boxes and Sheets</description></item></channel></rss>